Want to want to make the policing system and record taking as simple as it can it. We will achieve this by making a dockting system where a case reported will be recorded into a cloud and will be accessible across the lenght and breath of the country of by authorized persons. In the system, every station will be given a computer quiped with peripherials such as, cameras, fingerprint scanners and microphones for audio samples.

We want to be able to 
# Write reports into a complete docket such that on submit, a pdf is generated container all information including audiovisual elements.
#Can receieve calls and track location of caller in real time
#Distribute freshly reports across all nodes and made accessible by all authorized people
#

On the home 

Login/logout area
	Officer's credentials shall be checked against staff ID and Face ID or fingerprint
	
Date and Time, station code
	text input area


button to creat a new docket:
	when a new docket is started, user can:
	insert picture of reportee or other evidence
	attach scanned fingerprints
	time, date, reporting station, officer reporting shall be set by default.


Authorized Officer can be able to search system for records of suspects and past history of a suspect.
Information on officer to be taken:
	First Name
	Middle Name (If Any)
	Last Name
	Personal Contact
	Email
	House Address
	Rank
	Station currently posted
	Qualification
	Date of Birth
	Staff Id
	District, Regional, National Code
	Department currently working at eg: CID, PIP etc...
	Photo
	
Information of people to be stored:
	Name In full
	Place of birth
	Ghana Card Number
	House Address
	Employment status and place of work if any, duration of work time
	Criminal History
	last time seen or arrested or tickted
	-----------------------------------------------------------------
	
	Informations to display in preview search
	Name
	Category: Criminal, Civil, Treason, Protests, Complainant

Basic Functionalities
	Search system
	Authentications and logins.
	writing to pdfs and generatng customized pdf files
	Display current time, day and station id


*******************************************************************
Dockets Form Page
***********************
Officer is able to write report or case of incidence.
Officer attaches relevant data to the docket via attachments.

******pdf file****
# The file will be saved as print ready pdf file protect by a password only accessbile by station officer and reporting officer/CID/
# The header will container the name of the officer which is an input gotten from the login details, whoever logs in will be the registring    	officer
# The head will contain informstions of such, date and time and day in words, station code, district and city/town
# The header will contain also the police logo or the security agency logo/emblem mostly on the right side in black and white
# Then comes the body with all in-depth details
# All text content will appear typed with a type writer to indicate strong secrecy and force
# 
When officer registere's docket, it generates a preview to make sure everything is correct.


	
	